<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sports Event Management</string>


    <string name="create_one"><b><u>Create One</u></b></string>

    <string-array name="termsArray">
        <item><b>1. Introduction\n</b></item>
        <item>1.1. These are the terms of use, including the terms and conditions
of supply (Terms), for the NightMap application. For the purposes of
these Terms, both the website and application shall be referred to
as the "App". The App is operated by Night Map trading as
NightMap (we, us and our company). We are a simple partnership,
governed by art. 530 et seq. of the Swiss Code of Obligations.\n</item>
        <item>1.2. Your use of the App is subject to these Terms and you agree to
be bound by them. Use of your personal information submitted via
this App is governed by our Privacy Policy.\n</item>
        <item>1.3. We reserve the right to change these Terms from time to time
by changing them on the App. Your continued use of the App a will
be bound by the new Terms.\n</item>
        <item>1.4. As a consumer, nothing in these Terms will prevent you or stop
you from being able to enforce or receive the full benefit of your
legal rights provided under general Swiss law (your \"non-excludable
statutory rights\").\n</item>
        <item>1.5. By accessing, downloading, using, purchasing, or subscribing
to the NightMap Service, you acknowledge that you have read,
understood and agreed to be bound by the Terms and Conditions,
including the NightMap Privacy Policy (together, these "terms"). If
you are not eligible, or do not agree to these Terms, then you do
not have our permission to use the App.\n</item>
        <item>1.6. As a condition of use, you promise not to use the App for any
purpose that is prohibited by these Terms of Use. You are
responsible for all of your activity in connection with the App.
Additionally, you shall abide by all applicable local, state, national
and international laws and regulations and, if you represent a
business, any advertising, marketing, privacy, or other
self-regulatory code(s) applicable to your industry.\n</item>
        <item><b>2. The basics\n</b></item>
        <item>2.1 To use the App, you must be 16 or over. By continuing to use
the App and agreeing to these Terms you are representing to us
that you are 16 and we can rely on this representation. Additionally,
to fall within the eligibility criteria, you must not have been
previously suspended or removed from the App. Finally, any
registration for and use of the App is in compliance with all
applicable laws and regulations.\n</item>
        <item>2.2 If you are using the App on behalf of an entity, organisation, or
company, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to
bind that organisation to these Terms and you agree to be bound by
these Terms on behalf of that organisation. NightMap may, in its
sole discretion, refuse to offer the App to any person or entity, and
may change its eligibility criteria at any time.\n</item>
        <item>2.3 The App is only directed at people who access the App. While
the App helps you on choosing the best Venue for a given night and
provides you with further facilitates such as Reviews and Catch,
you should be careful to take a good judgement on the Venue
suitability. All actions are undertaken at your own initiative and
responsibility.\n</item>
        <item>2.4 We grant you a limited license to use the App to access and use
our services for your own personal and non-commercial use,
provided that you comply fully with these Terms. Subject to your
complete and ongoing compliance with all the terms and conditions
set forth in the Terms (including, without limitation, payment of any
applicable fees and compliance with all license restrictions),
NightMap grants you: (1) a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable,
non-sub licensable, revocable license to use one copy of the App
downloaded directly from NightMap or from a legitimate
marketplace or Distributor (such as Apple’s App Store or Google
Play Store), solely in object code format and solely for your
personal use for lawful purposes, on a single compatible mobile
device that you own or control; and (2) permission to access and
use the Service, only for your personal use, and solely through the
use of a licensed copy of the App. You may not reproduce,
distribute, publicly display, or publicly perform the App or any part of
the Service. Except if, and solely to the extent that, such a
restriction is impermissible under applicable law, you may not (a)
decompile, reverse engineer, or otherwise access or attempt to
access the source code for the App, or make or attempt to make
any modification to or derivative work of the App; or (b) interfere
with or circumvent any feature of the App, including without
limitation any security or access control mechanism. You may not
use the App or the Service for any purpose other than a purpose for
which the App and the Service are expressly designed. The term
App, as used herein, includes any update or modification to the App
made available to you by NightMap (unless provided with separate
terms). If you are prohibited under applicable law from using the
App or the Service, you may not use them.\n</item>
        <item>2.5 We reserve the right to prevent you using the App, however we
will honour your historic activity, unless you have not complied with
these Terms or we are unable to because of circumstances outside
our control. For more on this, please read below.</item>
        <item>2.6 Your use of the App may be subject to separate third party
terms of service and fees, including, without limitation, the terms of
service and data, SMS, MMS, and other fees of your mobile
network operator (the "Carrier"), which are your sole responsibility.</item>
        <item>2.7 The App is provided "as is" without warranties of any kind, and
NightMap’s liability to you is limited.\n</item>
        <item>2.8 By registering the account with NightMap, you consent to the
collection and use of your personally identifiable information in
accordance with NightMap’s Privacy Policy, including, without
limitation, the collection of information regarding purchases.\n</item>
        <item>2.9 There is currently no charge for the use of the App, except the
case in which the users buy tickets through the platform (Platform).\n</item>
        <item>2.10. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change these Terms
on a going-forward basis at any time. Please check these Terms
periodically for changes. In the event that a change to these Terms
materially modifies your rights or obligations, we will make
reasonable efforts to notify you of such change. We may provide
notice through a pop-up or banner within the Service, by sending an
email to any address you may have used to register for an account,
or through other similar mechanisms. Additionally, if the changed
Terms materially modify your rights or obligations, we may require
you to provide consent by accepting the changed Terms. If we
require your acceptance of the changed Terms, changes are
effective only after your acceptance. If you do not accept the
changed Terms, we may terminate your access to and use of the
App. All other changes are effective upon publication of the
changed Terms. Disputes arising under these Terms will be
resolved in accordance with the version of these Terms that was in
effect at the time the dispute arose.\n</item>
        <item>2.11 By using the App, you agree to receive certain electronic
communications from us as further described in our Privacy Policy.
Please read our Privacy Policy to learn more about your choices
regarding our electronic communications practices. You agree that
any notices, agreements, disclosures, or other communications that
we send to you electronically will satisfy any legal communication
requirements, including that those communications be in writing.\n</item>
        <item>2.12 Open Source Software. The App may include open source
software or third party software. Any such software is made
available to you under the terms of the applicable licenses. Please
review the information below for the applicable notices and license
terms.\n</item>
        <item>2.13 You are solely responsible for your interaction with other
users. You understand that the company currently does not conduct
criminal background checks or screenings on its users. The
company also does not inquire into the backgrounds of all of its
users or attempt to verify the statement of its users. The company
makes no representations or warranties as to the conduct of users
or their compatibility with any current or future users. The company
reserves the right to conduct any criminal background check or
other screenings (such as sex offender register searches), at any
time and using available public records.\n</item>
        <item>2.14 You understand and agree that we may, but are not obligated
to, monitor or review any Content you post as part of an App. We
may delete any Content, in whole or in part, that in the sole
judgment of us violates this Agreement or may harm the reputation
of the App or ours.\n</item>
        <item><b>3. Use and Access to the App</b>\n</item>
        <item>3.1 We cannot guarantee the continuous, uninterrupted or error-free
operability of the App. There may be times when certain features,
parts or content of the App, or the entire App, become unavailable
(whether on a scheduled or unscheduled basis) or are modified,
suspended or withdrawn by us, in our sole discretion, without notice
to you. You agree that we will not be liable to you or to any third
party for any unavailability, modification, suspension or withdrawal
of the App, or any features, parts or content of the App.\n</item>
        <item>3.2 We may change the format and Content of the App from time to
time unilaterally. We reserve the right to modify, change, substitute
or withdraw any information on our App. You agree that your use of
the App is on an \'as is\' and \'as available\' basis and at your sole risk.\n</item>
        <item>3.3 You may only use the App for non-commercial use and only in
accordance with these Terms. You may retrieve and display content
from the App on a computer or mobile device screen, print and copy
individual pages. Additional terms may also apply to certain
features, parts or content of the App and, where they apply, they
will be displayed before you access the relevant features, parts or
content.\n</item>
        <item>3.4 Except to the extent expressly set out in these Terms, you are
not allowed to:\n\n\t
● Store pages of the App on a server or other storage device connected to a
network or create an electronic database by systematically downloading and
storing all or most of the pages of the App; or\n\t
● Remove or change any Content of the App or attempt to circumvent security or
interfere with the proper working of the App or the servers on which it is hosted.\n</item>
        <item>3.5 You must only use the App and anything available from the App
for lawful purposes (complying with all applicable laws and
regulations), in a responsible manner, and not in a way that might
damage our name or reputation or that of any of our affiliates.\n</item>
        <item>3.5.1 All rights granted to you under these Terms will terminate
immediately in the event that you have not followed your
responsibilities as required by them (legally known as a \"breach\").\n</item>
        <item><b>3. You are not allowed to:\n</b></item>

        <item>Act unlawfully against other users:\n</item>
        <item>Use the App for any illegal purpose or in violation of any local, state,
national, or international law; Violate, or encourage others to
violate, any right of a third party, including by infringing or
misappropriating any third party intellectual property right; Interfere
with security-related features of the App, including by: (1) disabling
or circumventing features that prevent or limit use or copying of any
content; or (2) reverse engineering or otherwise attempting to
discover the source code of any portion of the Service except to the
extent that the activity is expressly permitted by applicable law;
interfere with the operation of the App or any users enjoyment of
the App, including by: (a) uploading or otherwise any disseminating
virus, adware, spyware, worm, or other malicious code; (b) making
any unsolicited offer or advertisement to another user of the App,
including any informational announcements, charity requests, and
petitions for signatures; (c) attempting to collect, personal
information about another user or third party without consent; (d)
taking any action (directly or indirectly) that imposes or may impose
(as determined by App in its sole discretion) an unreasonable or
disproportionately large load on NightMap’s or its third party
providers infrastructure; or (e) interfering with or disrupting any
network, equipment, or server connected to or used to provide the
App, or violating any regulation, policy, or procedure of any
network, equipment, or server; Perform any fraudulent activity,
including impersonating any person or entity or claiming a false
affiliation; Misrepresenting the source, identity or content of
information transmitted via the App; Accessing any other App
account without permission, or falsifying your age or date of birth;
Sell or otherwise transfer the access granted under these Terms, or
any right or ability to view, access, or use any part of the App;
Attempt to do any of the acts described in this Section, or assist or
permit any person in engaging in any of the acts described in this
Section, or impersonate any person or entity by:\n\t</item>
        <item>● solicit money from any users;
● \"stalk\" or otherwise harass any person;\n\t
● express or imply that any statements you make are endorsed by the Company
without our specific prior written consent;\n\t
● use the App in an illegal manner or to commit an illegal act;\n\t
● access the App in a jurisdiction in which it is illegal or unauthorized;\n\t</item>
        <item>● ask or use users to conceal the identity, source, or destination of any illegally
gained money or products;\n\t
● use any robot, spider, site search/retrieval application, or other manual or
automatic device or process to retrieve, index, \"data mine\", or in any way
reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the App or
its Content;\n\t
● collect usernames and/or email addresses of users by electronic or other means
for the purpose of sending unsolicited email or unauthorized framing of or linking
to the App;\n\t
● interfere with or disrupt the App or the servers or networks connected to the App;\n\t
● email or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or any
other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the
functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications
equipment;\n\t
● forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of
any information transmitted to or through the App (either directly or indirectly
through use of third party software);\n\t
● \"frame\" or \"mirror\" any part of the App, without the Company\'s prior written
authorization;\n\t
● use meta tags or code or other devices containing any reference to the Company
or the App (or any trademark, trade name, service mark, logo or slogan of the
Company) to direct any person to any other website for any purpose;\n\t
● modify, adapt, sublicense, translate, sell, reverse engineer, decipher, decompile
or otherwise disassemble any portion of the App or any software used on or for
the App, or cause others to do so;\n\t
● post, use, transmit or distribute, directly or indirectly, (e.g. screen scrape) in any
manner or media any content or information obtained from the App other than
solely in connection with your use of the App in accordance with this Agreement;\n\t</item>
        <item><b>4. Registering a NightMap Account and Information Sharing:\n</b></item>
        <item>4.1 In order to access NightMap facilities and make best use of the
App, you need to register the account by providing information
described in the Privacy Policy (such as name, nickname, email
address or other contact information). However, we reserve the
right to decline a new registration or cancel your account at any
time (including if you don\'t provide us with a valid email address
that is personal to you, or if you don\'t provide us with a correct
name and surname).\n</item>
        <item>4.2 To register an account you will need to fill out a form on the
mobile app or online, once applicable. You warrant that the
information you input is true, complete and accurate. You will
promptly inform us of any changes to such information (you can do
this by updating your account details at any time). The personal
information you give us is governed by our privacy policy.\n</item>
        <item>4.3 In order to register and access your account, you will need to
choose a password. It is important you keep this password
confidential because you are entirely responsible if you do not
maintain the confidentiality of your password to a reasonably
expected standard. Let us know as soon as you become aware
there has been a breach of security and we will suspend your
account. You agree that any person who you directly or implicitly
permit to use your password (implicitly, for example, because you
do not logout of your account and another person uses your device
to conduct any activity on the app or you write your password on a
noticeboard in your home and a family member then uses it to gain
access to your account) is authorised to act as your agent to use
the App and proceed any activity. If sensitive information is
revealed to unrelated parties, please undertake necessary steps
and notify us of a password change or that security has been
compromised.\n</item>
        <item>4.4 One individual user is allowed to register only one account on
the App. You warrant that you will not create fraudulent accounts.
You also warrant that you will not use any fraudulent activities to
generate unfair Reward Credits in the App to be applied to you (for
instance, you will not redeem your own invitation code with a
different account of yours).\n</item>
        <item>4.5 In order to download the App, you may be required by the third
party who is distributing or providing you access to the App, such as
Apple, Inc. or Google Inc. (each, a "Distributor") to create an
account. You are solely responsible for maintaining the security of
any logins, passwords, or other credentials that you select or that
are provided to you to access your account with any Distributor.
Your use of any account with a Distributor is subject to any terms,
conditions, and policies, including privacy policies, of that
Distributor. NightMap is not responsible for any act or omission of
any Distributor.\n</item>
        <item>4.6 In consideration of your use of our App, you agree that Your
Information:\n</item>
        <item>(a) shall not be fraudulent; (b) shall not infringe any third party\'s copyright, patent,
trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy; (c)
shall not violate any law, statute, ordinance or regulation; (d) shall not be defamatory,
trade libellous, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing; (e) shall not be obscene or
contain, pornography, child pornography, or photographs of unclothed person(s); (f) shall
not contain any viruses, trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots, easter eggs or
other computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with,
surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information; (g) shall
not create liability for us or cause us to lose (in whole or in part) the services of our ISPs
or other suppliers; (h) shall not link directly or indirectly to any materials to which you do
not have a right to link to or include. In addition, you agree that you will provide us with
your valid, current email address, both at the time of your registration with us and from
time to time as your email address changes.\n</item>
        <item>4.7 Except as otherwise provided in our Privacy Policy, we will not
sell, rent or otherwise disclose any of your Personally Identifiable
Information (as defined in our Privacy Policy) about you (including
your email address) to any third party.\n</item>
        <item>4.8 The information that you post to the App is intended for public
consumption, including your live ratings, reviews, photos, check-ins,
going-to, comments, likes, friends, lists, compliments, and account
profile etc. According to your preferences, some features can be
adjusted to Private Mode available to your friends only. In-App
Messenger and Catch function shall be for private use only and not
publicly displayed. If you decide to share on Facebook certain
check-ins or content, then you might be entitled to a reward by the
Managers of the relevant Venues, such promotions being available
and notified from time to time by the relevant Managers.\n</item>
        <item>4.9 Each of your check-ins using the App is saved to your \"Check-in
History,\" which allows you and your friends to look back at all the
locations you have checked in since you created your App account.
You can delete any or all of your check-ins from the check-in details
page on our website and in the App. If for some reason you ever
decide to delete your App account, your entire check-in history will
be removed from our database.\n</item>
        <item>4.10 Friends on NightMap can see, for example, your location (as
described in more detail below), name, email, phone number,
profile photo, hometown, a list of your friends, plans you write or
comment on, photos you post, reviews you write, live ratings you
post, check-ins, going to function, after party mode, traffic light in
the check-out function and which NightMap Services you use. Also,
through the ‘Catch’ function, if you swipe right to say "yes" in the
Check-out function to a person, you will be able to chat with that
person if they swipe right to you, i.e., when you "Catch" someone. If
you chat with your Catch, she/he will see the content of your chat.\n</item>
        <item>4.11 Individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it to
other individuals or entities without our control and without your
knowledge. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including
any specific information you may deem private in comments, plans
or tips or other content (location or otherwise) that you create in the
App. Please read our Privacy Policy for further information.\n</item>
        <item><b>5. Intellectual Property Rights\n</b></item>
        <item>5.1 All intellectual property rights (which includes rights such as
copyright, and rights in trademarks) in any content of the App
(including text, graphics, software, photographs and other images,
videos, sound, trademarks and logos) are owned by us and/or our
licensors. Except as expressly set out in these Terms, nothing in
these Terms gives you any rights in respect of any intellectual
property owned by us or our licensors and you acknowledge that
you do not acquire any ownership rights by downloading content
from the App. If you print off, copy or store pages from the App
(only as permitted by these Terms and Conditions), you must
ensure that any copyright, trademark or other intellectual property
right notices contained in the original content are reproduced.\n</item>
        <item>5.2 You agree that by submitting any posting, images or other
content for publication on the App (Your Content), you retain any
copyright you may have in Your Content, however you grant us and
our affiliates a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, non-exclusive,
royalty-free and fully sub-licensable right and license to use,
reproduce, edit, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative
works from, distribute, perform and display such content (in whole
or in part) and/or to incorporate it into other works in any form,
media or technology, whether for commercial or non-commercial
purposes. You waive any moral rights you may have in, or to be
identified as the author, of Your Content.\n</item>
        <item>5.3 You are solely responsible for Your Content (including content
you share with other sites, such as social networking sites) and we
do not endorse Your Content or any opinion, recommendation, or
advice expressed therein, and we expressly disclaim any and all
liability in connection with Your Content.\n</item>
        <item>5.4 In terms of our ownership and proprietary rights, this App is
owned and operated by NightMap. The visual interfaces, graphics,
design, compilation, information, data, computer code (including
source code or object code), products, software, services, and all
other elements of the App ("Materials") provided by NightMap are
protected by intellectual property and other laws. All Materials
contained in the App are the property of NightMap or our third-party
licensors. Except as expressly authorized by NightMap, you may
not make use of the Materials. NightMap reserves all rights to the
Materials not granted expressly in these Terms.\n</item>
        <item><b>6. Review Forums\n</b></item>
        <item>6.1 The App may, from time to time, make message boards,
newsgroups and/or other public forums (collectively Review
Forums) available to you so that you can feedback on Events
offered on the App and read the feedback submitted by other users
of the App. We do not control the material submitted to Review
Forums (collectively Postings), nor are Review Forums moderated.
You are solely responsible for the content of your Postings as
submitted by you and acknowledge that all Postings express the
views of their respective authors, and not our views.\n</item>
        <item>If you participate in any Review Forum, you must:\n\t</item>
        <item>● keep all Postings relevant to the purpose of the Review Forum and the nature of
any topic;\n\t
● not submit any Posting that is unlawful, threatening, abusive, libellous,
pornographic, obscene, vulgar, indecent, offensive or which infringes on the
intellectual property rights or other rights of any person;\n\t
● not submit any Posting that contains any viruses and/or other code that has
contaminating or destructive elements;\n\t
● not submit any Posting containing any form of advertising; and\n\t
● not impersonate, or misrepresent an affiliation with, any person or entity.\n\t</item>
        <item>You agree that, by submitting any Posting, you grant us and our
affiliates a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, non-exclusive,
royalty-free and fully sub-licensable right and license to use,
reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works
from, distribute, perform and display such Posting (in whole or part)
and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media or
technology, and you waive any moral rights you may have in, or to
be identified as the author, of such Posting.\n</item>
        <item>Whilst we do not screen or monitor Postings, we reserve the right,
in our sole discretion, to delete, edit or modify any Posting
submitted by you and/or to close any topic, at any time without
notice to you.\n</item>
        <item>Complaints about the content of any Posting must be sent to
nightmapgeneva@gmail.com and must contain details of the
specific Posting giving rise to the complaint.\n</item>
        <item><b>7. External Links\n</b></item>
        <item>7.1 The App may, from time to time, include links to external sites.
We have included links to these sites to provide you with access to
information and services that you may find useful or interesting. We
are not responsible for the content of these sites or for anything
provided by them and do not guarantee that they will be
continuously available. The fact that we include links to such
external sites does not imply any endorsement of or association
with their operators.\n</item>
        <item><b>8. Your Personal Information\n</b></item>
        <item>8.1 Use of your personal information submitted via the App is
governed by our Privacy Policy.\n</item>
        <item><b>9. Our Service Standards\n</b></item>
        <item>9.1 We warrant that we will exercise reasonable care and skill in
performing our obligations under these Terms. Provided we have
done so, we shall not be liable for errors or omissions. In the event
of an error or omission we will use reasonable endeavours to
correct any errors or omissions as soon as reasonably practicable
after we become aware.\n</item>
        <item>9.2 Except as expressly stated in these Terms, all warranties,
conditions or other terms, whether express or implied by statute or
common law or otherwise are excluded to the fullest extent
permitted by law. This does not stop you from exercising your legal
rights under general law to the extent that we cannot lawfully
exclude them, or claiming any remedies you might be entitled to
under general law.\n</item>
        <item>9.3 Users can buy certain tickets through the Platform. Users
accept to pay the relevant cost as indicated by the Platform with
respect to the purchase of the relevant ticket.\n</item>
        <item>9.4 NightMap is not responsible if the Venue does not admit the
ticket holder to the Venue because of reasons not depending on
NightMap. It is under the buyer\'s responsibility to comply with the
terms of entrance and rules of the relevant Venues (e.g. dress
code, entry time etc.) and NightMap we can not guarantee nor be
held liable if the ticket holder is not admitted because of
non-compliance with the Venue\'s standard rules.\n</item>
        <item><b>10. Liability\n</b></item>
        <item>10.1 In no event shall we be liable to you for any business losses
(and loss of profits shall always be treated as a type of business
loss) and any liability we do have for losses you suffer. Further, our
liability to you for any and all losses however they arise in
connection with these Terms and your use of the App is strictly
limited to losses that were reasonably foreseeable. Losses are
foreseeable where they could be contemplated by you and us at the
time your order is accepted by us.\n</item>
        <item>10.2 Other than as expressly described in these Terms, A&amp;A.make
Ltd does not warrant and excludes all liability in respect of, or to
provide, including in respect of the quality, safety, usability or any
other aspect of the Events in respect of which a Ticket is or may be
redeemed. We do, however, issue credits and refunds in limited
circumstances (see section Our Refunds Policy).\n</item>
        <item>10.3 We will not be liable or responsible for any failure to perform,
or delay in performance of, any of our obligations that are caused
by events outside our reasonable control.\n</item>
        <item>10.4 Where pictures, reviews, statistics, ratings and descriptions
are displayed they are intended to be purely representative of the
Venue. Your actual experience may vary.\n</item>
        <item>10.5 We are not responsible for the conduct of any user. In no
event shall the App, its affiliates or its partners be liable (directly or
indirectly) for any losses or damages whatsoever, whether direct,
indirect, general, special, compensatory, consequential, and/or
incidental, arising out of or relating to the conduct of you or anyone
else in connection with the use of the App, including, without
limitation, death, bodily injury, emotional distress, and/or any other
damages resulting from communications or meetings with other
users or persons you meet through the App. You agree to take all
necessary precautions in all interactions with other users,
particularly if you decide to communicate off the App or meet in
person, or if you decide to send money to another user. You
understand that We make no guarantees, either express or implied,
regarding your ultimate compatibility with individuals you meet
through the App. You should not provide your financial information
(for example, your credit card or bank account information), or wire
or otherwise send money, to other users.\n</item>
        <item>10.6 You agree that NightMap shall not be responsible or liable for
any unauthorized access to, alteration or use of your account,
transmissions or data, or any material or data sent or received or
not sent or received through the Platform. You agree that NightMap
is not responsible or liable for any threatening, defamatory,
obscene, offensive, illegal or other content or conduct of any third
party or any infringement of another\'s rights, including intellectual
property rights.\n</item>
        <item>NightMap (or its affiliates, licensors and suppliers), as a mere web
based platform, under no circumstances or in any event will be held
liable concerning any subject matter related to the Platform,
regardless of the form of any claim or action, tort, whether in
contract, negligence, strict liability or otherwise, for any (a) matter
beyond its reasonable control, including, but not limited to, any loss,
damages, death or personal injury to the attendants of the Event
taking place at the Venues. The Managers shall be solely
responsible for managing the relevant Venues, the relevant Events
and shall ensure compliance with the applicable safety standards.
Such terms shall be applicable also in case NightMap shall
organize events at the said Venues, in agreement with the relevant
Managers (b) loss or inaccuracy of data, loss or interruption of use,
or cost of procuring substitute technology, goods or services (c)
indirect, punitive, incidental, reliance, special, exemplary or
consequential damages including, but not limited to, loss of
business, revenues, profits or goodwill.\n</item>
        <item><b>11. Suspension and termination\n</b></item>
        <item>11.1 We may suspend or terminate all or part of your use of the App
and your account if you use (or permit anyone other than you to
use) the App or your account in breach of these Terms and we do
not reasonably consider that your breach can be resolved, or if it
can be resolved you have failed to resolve it to our reasonable
satisfaction after we have asked you to do so and given you a
reasonable opportunity to do so.\n</item>
        <item>11.2 Termination shall not prejudice any other right or remedy you
or We may have in respect of accrued rights (including rights in
respect of any breach) or liabilities, which arose prior to termination.\n</item>
        <item>11.3 In addition, NightMap may in its sole discretion terminate your
account on the App or suspend or terminate your access to the App
at any time, with or without notice. We also reserve the right to
modify, update, or discontinue the App at any time (including by
limiting or discontinuing certain features of the App) without notice
to you. Should NightMap update the App, you consent to automatic
updating on your device through the App, and agree that the terms
and conditions of this Agreement will apply to all such updates.
NightMap will have no liability whatsoever on account of any
change to the App or any suspension or termination of your access
to or use of the App. You may terminate your account at any time
by contacting customer service at nightmapgeneva@gmail.com or
deleting your account on the App.\n</item>
        <item><b>12. General\n</b></item>
        <item>12.1 These Terms are personal to you. You may not transfer or
assign any or all of your rights or obligations under these Terms to
any other person without our consent.\n</item>
        <item>12.2 All notices given by you to us must be given in writing to the
address set out at the end of these Terms. We may give notice to
you at either the email or postal address you provide to us when
placing an order.\n</item>
        <item>12.3 If we fail to enforce any of our rights, it does not result in a
waiver of that right.\n</item>
        <item>12.4 If any provision of these Terms is found to be unenforceable,
that provision shall be struck out and where capable all other
provisions shall remain in force unaffected.\n</item>
        <item>12.5 These Terms may not be varied except with our express
written consent.\n</item>
        <item>12.6 These Terms and any document expressly referred to in them
constitute the entire agreement between you and us about the
subject matter of these Terms and, in relation to such subject
matter, supersedes and extinguishes all earlier understandings and
agreements between you and us and all earlier representations by
us, including any innocent or negligent misrepresentations. We do
not limit our liability to you for any fraudulent misrepresentations
made by us in these Terms or otherwise.\n</item>
        <item>12.7 All provisions of these Terms apply equally to and are for the
benefit of A&amp;A.make Ltd, its group members (which means, in
relation to A&amp;A.make Ltd, any \"group undertaking\" as defined in
section 1161 of the Companies Act) and the Merchants at any
relevant time and each shall have the right to enforce such
provisions directly or on its own behalf (save that these Terms may
be varied or rescinded without the consent of the group members
and the Merchants). Subject to the previous sentence, no term of
this Agreement is otherwise enforceable pursuant to the Contracts
(Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999 by any person who is not a party
to it.\n</item>
        <item><b>13. Dispute Resolution\n</b></item>
        <item>13.1 In the first instance we request that you contact us
(nightmapgeneva@gmail.com) if you have a complaint against us
and we shall try to resolve it.\n</item>
        <item>13.2 This Terms and Conditions and any dispute or claim arising
out of or in connection with it or its subject matter or formation
(including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by
and construed in accordance with the law of England and Wales.\n</item>
        <item>13.3 Each party irrevocably agrees that the courts of England and
Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction to settle any dispute or claim
that arises out of or in connection with this agreement or its subject
matter or formation (including non-contractual disputes or claims).\n</item>
        <item><b>14. Indemnity\n</b></item>
        <item>14.1 You agree that you will be responsible for your use of the App,
and you agree to defend and indemnify NightMap and its officers,
directors, employees, consultants, affiliates, subsidiaries and
agents (together, the \"NightMap Entities\") from and against every
claim, liability, damage, loss, and expense, including reasonable
attorneys\' fees and costs, arising out of or in any way connected
with: (a) your access to, use of, or alleged use of, the App; (b) your
violation of any portion of these Terms, any representation,
warranty, or agreement referenced in these Terms, or any
applicable law or regulation; (c) your violation of any third-party
right, including any intellectual property right or publicity,
confidentiality, other property, or privacy right; or (d) any dispute or
issue between you and any third party. We reserve the right, at our
own expense, to assume the exclusive defence and control of any
matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you (without limiting
your indemnification obligations with respect to that matter), and in
that case, you agree to cooperate with our defence of that claim.\n</item>
        <item><b></b></item>
        <item>15. Additional Terms relating to Apple\n</item>
        <item>If you download, access and/or use the App on Apple\'s iOS
operating system:\n</item>
        <item>15.1 The App may only be accessed and used on a device owned
or controlled by you and using Apple\'s iOS operating system, and
only in accordance with Apple’s usage rules published in its App
Store terms of service.\n</item>
        <item>15.2 You acknowledge and agree that:\n</item>
        <item>a) Apple has no obligation at all to provide any support or
maintenance services in relation to the App. If you have any
maintenance or support questions in relation to the App, please
contact us (nightmapgeneva@gmail.com) not Apple, using the
details in these Terms;\n</item>
        <item>b) Except as otherwise expressly set out in these Terms, any claims
relating to the possession or use of the App are between you and
us (and not between you, or anyone else, and Apple);\n</item>
        <item>c) In the event of any claim by a third party that your possession or
use (in accordance with these Terms) of the App infringes any
intellectual property rights, Apple will not be responsible or liable to
you in relation to that claim; and\n</item>
        <item>d) Although these Terms are entered into between you and us (and
not Apple), Apple, as a third-party beneficiary under these Terms,
will have the right to enforce these Terms against you.\n</item>
        <item>15.3 You represent and warrant that:\n</item>
        <item>a) You are not, and will not be, located in any country that is the
subject of UN and EU sanctions, embargoes or that has been
designated by the UN or EU as a \"terrorist supporting\" country; and</item>
        <item>b) You are not listed on any UN and EU list of prohibited or
restricted parties.\n</item>
        <item>15.4 If the App does not conform to any warranty applying to it, you
may notify Apple, which will then refund the purchase price of the
App (if any) to you. Subject to that, and to the maximum extent
permitted by law, Apple does not give or enter into any warranty,
condition or other term in relation to the App and will not be liable to
you for any claims, losses, costs or expenses of whatever nature in
relation to the App or as a result of you or anyone else using the
App or relying on any of its content.\n</item>
        <item><b>16. Parties at Venues\n</b></item>
        <item>16.1 Through our App we provide you with the ability to locate the
party in the city of your choice that is happening at the venue
included in our app (either existing in our database or added
manually by the users). Please acknowledge that we do not
supervise these parties and are not involved in any way with the
actions of any individuals at these parties. As a result, we have no
control over the identity or actions of the individuals who are
present at a NightMap Party, and we request that our users
exercise caution and good judgment when attending any NightMap
Party.\n</item>
        <item>16.2 Because we do not supervise or control the parties or
interactions among or between members of NightMap users and
other persons or companies, and because we are not involved in
any way with physical transportation to or from parties or with the
actions of any individuals at parties, and because we do not control
any third party providers such as Amazon.com, PayPal, credit card
companies or other payment processing companies, and because
we cannot guarantee the true identity, age, nationality of App users,
and because we have very limited control, if any, over the quality,
safety, morality, legality, truthfulness or accuracy of various aspects
of the App you agree that you bear all risk and you agree to release
us (and our officers, directors, shareholders, agents, employees,
affiliates, subsidiaries, and third party partners) from claims,
demands, and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind
and nature, known and unknown, suspected and unsuspected,
disclosed and undisclosed, now and in the future, arising out of or in
any way connected with your use of the App, your Third Party
Transactions, our resolution of any disputes among users, and/or
your transportation to or from, attendance at, or the actions of you
or other persons at, a party.\n</item>
        <item><b>17. Warranties\n</b></item>
        <item>17.1 No information, whether oral or written, obtained by you from
the App or any materials or content available through the App will
create any warranty regarding any of the NightMap entities or the
App that is not expressly stated in these terms. You assume all risk
for any damage that may result from your use of or access to the
App, your dealing with any other service user, and any materials or
content available through the App. You understand and agree that
you use the service, access, download, or otherwise obtain
materials or content through the App and any associated sites or
services, at your own discretion and risk, and that you are solely
responsible for any damage to your property (including your
computer system or mobile device used in connection with the
App), or the loss of data that results from the use of the App or the
download or use of that material or content.\n</item>
        <item>17.2 Some jurisdictions may prohibit a disclaimer of warranties and
you may have other rights that vary from jurisdiction to jurisdiction.
In no event will the NightMap entities be liable to you for any
indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages
(including damages for loss of profits, goodwill, or any other
intangible loss) arising out of or relating to your access to or use of,
or your inability to access or use, the App or any materials or
content on the service, whether based on warranty, contract, tort
(including negligence), statute, or any other legal theory, and
whether or not any NightMap entity has been informed of the
possibility of damage.\n</item>
        <item><b>18. Trademarks; Copyrights; Proprietary Rights\n</b></item>
        <item>18.1 NightMap trademarks and service marks, and other NightMap
logos, products and service names, are trademarks of A&amp;A.make
Ltd. (the "A&amp;A.make Trademark"). Except as otherwise permitted
by law, you agree not to display or use in any manner the
A&amp;A.make Ltd Trademarks without A&amp;A.make Ltd\'s prior written
consent.\n</item>
        <item>18.2 NightMap respects the intellectual property of others, and we
ask our users to do the same. To the extent NightMap uses a
trademark that is the property of a third party, NightMap shall
provide clear notice to anyone viewing NightMap’s use of that
trademark that (a) NightMap does not own the trademark and that
the trademark is the property of a third party, (b) NightMap has no
affiliation, connection or association with that third party, and (c) if
applicable, that third party has not approved or sponsored
NightMap’s use of the trademark in any way. We may, in
appropriate circumstances and in our discretion, remove, or disable
access to, material that infringes on the rights of others, and
terminate access to our App to those who may be repeat infringers.
If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that
constitutes copyright infringement, or your intellectual property
rights have been otherwise violated, please provide us on the
following email nightmapgeneva@gmail.com with the following
information: 1.an electronic or physical signature of the person
authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other
intellectual property interest; 2.a description of the copyrighted work
or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed; 3.a
description of where the material that you claim is infringing is
located on the site; 4.your address, telephone number, and email
address; 5.a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that
the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent,
or the law; 6.a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury,
that the above information in your Notice is accurate and that you
are the copyright or intellectual property owner or authorized to act
on the copyright or intellectual property owner\'s behalf.\n</item>
        <item><b>19. Language\n</b></item>
        <item>19.1 Where NightMap has provided you with a translation of the
English language version of these Terms of Use, then you agree
that the translation is provided for your convenience only and that
the English language versions of the Terms will govern your
relationship with NightMap.\n</item>
        <item>19.2 If there is any contradiction between what the English
language version of these Terms of Use says and what a
translation says, then the English language version shall take
precedence.\n</item>
        <item><b>20. Contact Us\n</b></item>
        <item>Please submit any questions you have about these Terms, an order
you have placed or purchasing in general by email to
nightmapgeneva@gmail.com\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="policyArray">
        <item>Welcome to NightMap’s Privacy Policy. Thank you for taking the
time to read it.\n</item>
        <item>We appreciate that you trust us with your information and we intend
to always keep that trust. This starts with making sure you
understand the information we collect, why we collect it, how it is
used and your choices regarding your information. This Policy
describes our privacy practices in plain language, keeping legal and
technical jargon to a minimum.\n</item>
        <item><b>1. WHO WE ARE\n</b></item>
        <item>The company that is responsible for your information under this
Privacy Policy (the \"data controller\") is Night Map.\n</item>
        <item><b>2. WHERE THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES\n</b></item>
        <item>This Privacy Policy applies to websites, apps, events and other
services operated by NightMap. For simplicity, we refer to all of
these as our \"services\" in this Privacy Policy.\n</item>
        <item><b>3. INFORMATION WE COLLECT\n</b></item>
        <item>It goes without saying, we can\'t help you find the best parties for
you, discover venues and meet like-minded people without some
information about you, such as basic profile details and the types of
people you\'d like to meet. We also collect information generated as
you use our services, for example access logs, as well as
information from third parties, like when you access our services
through a social media account. If you want additional info, we go
into more detail below.\n</item>
        <item><i>Information you give us</i>\n</item>
        <item>You choose to give us certain information when using our services.
This includes:\n</item>
        <item>\t● When you create an account, you provide us with at least your
login credentials, as well as some basic details necessary for
the service to work, such as your gender or date of birth.\n
\t● When you complete your profile, you can share with us
additional information, such as details on your personality,
interests and other details about you, as well as content such
as photos and videos. To add certain content, like pictures or
videos, you may allow us to access your camera or photo
album. Some of the information you choose to provide us may
be considered \"special\" or \"sensitive\" in certain jurisdictions,
for example your racial or ethnic origins, sexual orientation
and religious beliefs. By choosing to provide this information,
you consent to our processing of that information.\n
\t● When you make a purchase directly from us (rather than
through a platform such as iOS or Android), you provide us or
our payment service provider with information, such as your
debit or credit card number or other financial information.\n
\t● When you participate in surveys or focus groups, you give us
your insights into our products and services, responses to our
questions and testimonials.\n
\t● When you choose to participate in our promotions, events or
contests, we collect the information that you use to register or
enter.\n\t● If you contact our customer care team, we collect the
information you give us during the interaction. Sometimes, we
monitor or record these interactions for training purposes and
to ensure a high quality of service.\n
\t● If you ask us to communicate with or otherwise process
information of other people (for example, if you ask us to send
an email on your behalf to one of your friends), we collect the
information about others that you give us in order to complete
your request.\n
\t● Of course, we also process your chats with other users as well
as the content you publish, comments and likes as part of the
operation of the services.\n</item>
        <item><i>Information we receive from others\n</i></item>
        <item>In addition to the information you provide us directly, we receive
information about you from others, including:\n</item>
        <item>\t● Other Users\n
\t\t Other users may provide information about you as they use
our services. For instance, we may collect information about
you from other users if they contact us about you.\n
\t● Social Media\n
\t\t You may be able to use your social media login (such as
Facebook Login) to create and log into your NightMap
account. This saves you from having to remember yet another
user name and password and allows you to share some
information from your social media account with us.\n
\t● Other Partners\n
\t\t We may receive info about you from our partners, for instance
where NightMap ads are published on a partner\'s websites
and platforms (in which case they may pass along details on a
campaign\'s success).\n</item>
        <item><i>Information collected when you use our services\n</i></item>
        <item>When you use our services, we collect information about which
features you\'ve used, how you\'ve used them and the devices you
use to access our services. See below for more details:\n</item>
        <item>\t● Usage Information\n
\t\t We collect information about your activity on our services, for
instance how you use them (e.g., date and time you logged in,
features you\'ve been using, searches, clicks and pages which
have been shown to you, referring webpage address,
advertising that you click on) and how you interact with other
users (e.g., users you connect and interact with, time and date
of your messages, number of posts you upload).\n\t● Device information\n\t\t We collect information from and about the device(s) you use
to access our services, including:\n</item>
        <item>\t\t\t○ hardware and software information such as IP address,
device ID and type, device-specific and apps settings
and characteristics, app crashes, advertising IDs (such
as Google’s AAID and Apple\'s IDFA, both of which are
randomly generated numbers that you can reset by
going into your device’ settings), browser type, version
and language, operating system, time zones, identifiers
associated with cookies or other technologies that may
uniquely identify your device or browser;\n
\t\t\t○ information on your wireless and mobile network
connection, like your service provider and signal
strength;\n
\t\t\t○ information on device sensors such as accelerometers,
gyroscopes and compasses.\n</item>
        <item>\t● Other information with your consent\n
\t\t If you give us permission, we can collect your precise
geolocation (latitude and longitude) through various means,
depending on the service and device you’re using, including
GPS, Bluetooth or Wi-Fi connections. The collection of your
geolocation may occur in the background even when you
aren’t using the services if the permission you gave us
expressly permits such collection. If you decline permission for
us to collect your geolocation, we will not collect it.
Similarly, if you consent, we may collect your photos and
videos (for instance, if you want to publish a photo or a video
from a venue you visited) or comments about posted content
on the app.\n</item>
        <item><b>4. COOKIES AND OTHER SIMILAR DATA
COLLECTION TECHNOLOGIES\n</b></item>
        <item>We use and may allow others to use cookies and similar
technologies (e.g., web beacons, pixels) to recognise you and/or
your device(s). You may read our Cookie Policy at
https://www.NightMap.co/cookies for more information on why we
use them (such as authenticating you, remembering your
preferences and settings, analysing site traffic and trends,
delivering and measuring the effectiveness of advertising
campaigns, allowing you to use social features) and how you can
better control their use, through your browser settings and other
tools.\n</item>
        <item>Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox and
Chrome) have a \"Do Not Track\" (\"DNT\") feature that tells a website
that a user does not want to have his or her online activity tracked.
If a website that responds to a DNT signal receives a DNT signal,
the browser can block that website from collecting certain
information about the browser\'s user. Not all browsers offer a DNT
option and DNT signals are not yet uniform. For this reason, many
businesses, including NightMap, do not currently respond to DNT
signals.\n</item>
        <item><b>5. HOW WE USE INFORMATION\n</b></item>
        <item>The main reason we use your information is to deliver and improve
our services. Read on for a more detailed explanation of the various
reasons we use your information, together with practical examples.\n</item>
        <item><i>To administer your account and provide our services to you\n</i></item>
        <item>\t● Create and manage your account\n
\t● Provide you with customer support and respond to your
requests\n
\t● Complete your transactions\n
\t● Communicate with you about our services, including order
management and ticket delivery\n</item>
        <item><i>To help you connect with other users and create the nightlife
community\n</i></item>
        <item>\t● Show users\' profiles to one another\n
\t● Show content you have posted publicly (such as photos,
videos, check-ins posted from the venues or comments) on
the Party Feed. Some features can be adjusted to be shown
privately, making them visible to your friends only.\n</item>
        <item><i></i></item>
        <item>To provide new NightMap services to you\n</item>
        <item>\t● Register you and display your profile on new NightMap
features and apps\n
\t● Administer your account on these new features and apps\n</item>
        <item><i>To improve our services and develop new ones\n</i></item>
        <item>\t● Administer focus groups and surveys\n
\t● Conduct research and analysis of users’ behaviour to improve
our services and content (for instance, we may decide to
change the look and feel or even substantially modify a given
feature based on users\' behaviour)\n
\t● Develop new features and services (for example, we may
decide to build a new interests-based feature further to
requests received from users).\n</item>
        <item><i>To ensure legal compliance</i>\n</item>
        <item>\t● Comply with legal requirements\n
\t● Assist law enforcement\n
\t● Enforce or exercise our rights, for example our Terms\n</item>
        <item>To process your information as described above, we rely on the
following legal bases:\n</item>
        <item>\t● Provide our service to you: Most of the time, the reason we
process your information is to perform the contract that you
have with us. For instance, as you go about using our service
to find the best parties for you, discover venues and meet
like-minded people, we use your information to maintain your
account, your profile and posts, to make it viewable to other
users and recommend other users to you.\n
\t● Legitimate interests: We may use your information where we
have legitimate interests to do so. For instance, we analyse
users’ behaviour on our services to continuously improve our
offerings and we process information for administrative and
legal purposes.\n\t
● Consent: From time to time, we may ask for your consent to
use your information for certain specific reasons. You may
withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us at the
address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.\n</item>
        <item><b>6. HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION\n</b></item>
        <item>Since our goal is to help you find best parties for you and meet
like-minded people the main sharing of users’ information is, of
course, with other users. We also share some users’ information
with service providers and partners who assist us in operating the
services and, in some cases, legal authorities. Read on for more
details about how your information is shared with others.\n</item>
        <item>\t● With other users\n
\t\t You share information with other users when you voluntarily
disclose information on the service (including your public
profile and your posts). Please be careful with your information
and make sure that the content you share is stuff that you’re
comfortable being publicly viewable since neither you nor we
can control what others do with your information once you
share it.\n
\t\t If you choose to limit the audience for all or part of your profile
or for certain content or information about you, then it will be
visible according to your settings.\n\t● With other social networks\n
\t\t You share information with other users when you voluntarily
disclose information on the service (including your public
profile and your posts). Please be careful with your information
and make sure that the content you share is stuff that you’re
comfortable being publicly viewable since neither you nor we
can control what others do with your information once you
share it.\n
\t\t If you choose to limit the audience for all or part of your profile
or for certain content or information about you, then it will be
visible according to your settings.\n\t● With our service providers and partners\n
\t\t We use third parties to help us operate and improve our
services. These third parties assist us with various tasks,
including data hosting and maintenance, analytics, customer
care, marketing, advertising, payment processing and security
operations.\n
\t\t We may also share information with partners who distribute
and assist us in advertising our services. For instance, we
may share limited information on you in hashed, non-human
readable form to advertising partners.
We follow a strict vetting process prior to engaging any service
provider or working with any partner. All of our service
providers and partners must agree to strict confidentiality
obligations.\n\t● For corporate transactions\n
\t\t We may transfer your information if we are involved, whether
in whole or in part, in a merger, sale, acquisition, divestiture,
restructuring, reorganisation, dissolution, bankruptcy or other
change of ownership or control.\n\t● When required by law\n
\t\t We may disclose your information if reasonably necessary: (i)
to comply with a legal process, such as a court order,
subpoena or search warrant, government / law enforcement
investigation or other legal requirements; (ii) to assist in the
prevention or detection of crime (subject in each case to
applicable law); or (iii) to protect the safety of any person.\n\t● To enforce legal rights\n
\t\t We may also share information: (i) if disclosure would mitigate
our liability in an actual or threatened lawsuit; (ii) as necessary
to protect our legal rights and legal rights of our users,
business partners or other interested parties; (iii) to enforce
our agreements with you; and (iv) to investigate, prevent, or
take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or
other wrongdoing.\n\t● With your consent or at your request\n
\t\t We may ask for your consent to share your information with
third parties. In any such case, we will make it clear why we
want to share the information.\n
\t\t We may use and share non-personal information (meaning
information that, by itself, does not identify who you are such
as device information, general demographics, general
behavioral data, geolocation in de-identified form), as well as
personal information in hashed, non-human readable form,
under any of the above circumstances. We may also share
this information with third parties (notably advertisers) to
develop and deliver targeted advertising on websites or
applications of third parties. We may combine this information
with additional non-personal information or personal
information in hashed, non-human readable form collected
from other sources.\n</item>
        <item><b>7. CROSS-BORDER DATA TRANSFERS\n</b></item>
        <item>Sharing of information laid out in Section 6 “How We Share
Information” sometimes involves cross-border data transfers, for
instance to the United States of America and other jurisdictions. As
an example, where the service allows for users to be located in the
European Economic Area (“EEA”), their personal information is
transferred to countries outside of the EEA. We use standard
contract clauses approved by the European Commission or other
suitable safeguard to permit data transfers from the EEA to other
countries. Standard contractual clauses are commitments between
companies transferring personal data, binding them to protect the
privacy and security of your data\n</item>
        <item><b>8. YOUR RIGHTS</b></item>
        <item>We want you to be in control of your information, so we have
provided you with the following tools:\n</item>
        <item>\t● Access / Update tools in the service. Tools and account
settings that help you to access, rectify or delete information
that you provided to us and that’s associated with your
account directly within the service. If you have any question on
those tools and settings, please contact us at
nightmapgeneva@gmail.com\n
\t● Device permissions. Mobile platforms have permission
systems for specific types of device data and notifications,
such as phone book and location services as well as push
notifications. You can change your settings on your device to
either consent or oppose the collection of the corresponding
information or the display of the corresponding notifications.
Of course, if you do that, certain services may lose full
functionality.\n
\t● Deletion. You can delete your account by using the
corresponding functionality directly on the service.\n</item>
        <item>We want you to be aware of your privacy rights. Here are a few key
points to remember:\n</item>
        <item>\t● Reviewing your information. Applicable privacy laws may
give you the right to review the personal information we keep
about you (depending on the jurisdiction, this may be called
right of access, right of portability or variations of those terms).
You can request a copy of your personal information by
putting in such a request at nightmapgeneva@gmail.com\n
\t● Updating your information. If you believe that the
information we hold about you is inaccurate or that we are no
longer entitled to use it and want to request its rectification,
deletion or object to its processing, please contact us at
nightmapgeneva@gmail.com\n</item>
        <item>For your protection and the protection of all of our users, we may
ask you to provide proof of identity before we can answer the above
requests.\n</item>
        <item>Keep in mind, we may reject requests for certain reasons, including
if the request is unlawful or if it may infringe on trade secrets or
intellectual property or the privacy of another user. If you wish to
receive information relating to another user, such as a copy of any
messages you received from him or her through our service, the
other user will have to contact our team at
nightmapgeneva@gmail.com to provide their written consent before
the information is released.\n</item>
        <item>Also, we may not be able to accommodate certain requests to
object to the processing of personal information, notably where
such requests would not allow us to provide our service to you
anymore. For instance, we cannot provide our service if we do not
have your date of birth.\n</item>
        <item>\t● Uninstall. You can stop all information collection by an app by
uninstalling it using the standard uninstall process for your
device. If you uninstall the app from your mobile device, the
unique identifier associated with your device will continue to
be stored. If you re-install the application on the same mobile
device, we will be able to re-associate this identifier to your
previous activities.\n
\t● Accountability. In certain countries, including in the
European Union, you have a right to lodge a complaint with
the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns
about how we process your personal information. The data
protection authority you can lodge a complaint with notably
may be that of your habitual residence, where you work or
where we are established.\n</item>
        <item><b>9. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION\n</b></item>
        <item>We work hard to protect you from unauthorised access to or
alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information. As
with all technology companies, although we take steps to secure
your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect,
that your personal information will always remain secure.\n</item>
        <item>We regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and
attacks and regularly review our information collection, storage and
processing practices to update our physical, technical and
organisational security measures.\n</item>
        <item>We may suspend your use of all or part of the services without
notice if we suspect or detect any breach of security. If you believe
that your account or information is no longer secure, please notify
us immediately at nightmapgeneva@gmail.com\n</item>
        <item><b>10. HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR INFORMATION\n</b></item>
        <item>We keep your personal information only as long as we need it for
legitimate business purposes (as laid out in Section 5 “How We Use
Information”) and as permitted by applicable law. To protect the
safety and security of our users on and of our services, we
implement a safety retention window of three months following
account deletion. During this period, account information will be
retained although the account will of course not be visible on the
services anymore.\n</item>
        <item>In practice, we delete or anonymise your information upon deletion
of your account (following the safety retention window) or after three
years of continuous inactivity, unless:\n</item>
        <item>\t1. we must keep it to comply with applicable law (for instance,
some “traffic data” is kept for one year to comply with statutory
data retention obligations);\n
\t2. we must keep it to evidence our compliance with applicable
law (for instance, records of consents to our Terms, Privacy
Policy and other similar consents are kept for five years);\n
\t3. there is an outstanding issue, claim or dispute requiring us to
keep the relevant information until it is resolved; or\n
\t4. the information must be kept for our legitimate business
interests, such as fraud prevention and enhancing users\'
safety and security. For example, information may need to be
kept to prevent a user who was banned for unsafe behavior or
security incidents from opening a new account.\n</item>
        <item>Keep in mind that even though our systems are designed to carry
out data deletion processes according to the above guidelines, we
cannot promise that all data will be deleted within a specific time
frame due to technical constraints.\n</item>
        <item><b>11. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY\n</b></item>
        <item>Our services are restricted to users who are 16 years of age or
older. We do not permit users under the age of 16 on our platform
and we do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone
under the age of 16. If you suspect that a user is under the age of
16, please use the reporting mechanism available through the
service.\n</item>
        <item><b>12. PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES\n</b></item>
        <item>Because we’re always looking for new and innovative ways to help
you find the best parties, discover new venues and meet like
minded people, this policy may change over time. We will notify you
before any material changes take effect so that you have time to
review the changes.\n</item>
        <item><b>13. HOW TO CONTACT US\n</b></item>
        <item>If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, here’s how you can
reach us:\n</item>
        <item>Online:\n</item>
        <item>nightmapgeneva@gmail.com\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
        <string name="google_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">AIzaSyBDeSBsvnLmEuOAsIRuNA18Z-dYREq-45Q</string>

</resources>